Carla: So, your sister is visiting from the US?
Ben: Yeah… she’s going to meet Izzy this evening.
Carla: Are you nervous?
Emma: Hello, this is room thirteen.
Receptionist: How can I help you?
Emma: There’s a problem with the air conditioning.
It isn’t working and it’s very hot in my room.
Ben, Izzy can’t come with us.
She needs to meet some people from work.
Ben: Really, Izzy?
Do you really need to go to this work thing?
Izzy: Actually, I need to go now.
Izzy: Morning!
Ben: Morning.
Turn off the light!
Izzy: I think I left my phone charger here!
Ben: Yeah.
It’s there.
What time is it?
Izzy: It’s ten past seven.
Ben: You’re up early today.
Izzy: Actually, I’m late.
Don’t forget we’re having dinner with some people from work this evening.
Ben: I know.
Izzy: Do you remember where it is?
Ben: Les Amis, seven p.m.
Get there early.
Dress nicely.
Izzy: Thanks for coming this evening.
Ben: No problem.
Now… I’m going to go back to sleep.
My first class isn’t until ten today.
Hey! Where’s your helmet?
Izzy: I don’t need it.
I’m getting a taxi today.
I’m meeting an important client and I can’t be late.